Dhaka, Bangladesh M: +8801520100517

E: tanzilasultanarumki@gmail.com

KNOWLEDGE OF

Research methods

Statistical Analysis

Survey Supervision

Data Collection

Literature Review

STATA

.....

LaTex

SDG Financing

Blended Finance

R

MS Excel

PERSONAL SKILLS

Detail orientated

Resourceful

Perfectionist

Enthusiasm

Dexterous

Patience

1 unence

Intuitive

PERSONAL DETAILS

Tanzila Sultana Flat-15G, Meghna Bhaban Block-G, Zoo Road Mirpur-1, Dhaka - 1216

Tanzila Sultana

CAREER OBJECTIVE

As a research enthusiast from the beginning of her student life Tanzila Sultana wants to be a prominent researcher in Bangladesh. She obtained her knowledge and experiences on various steps of research like survey, survey supervision, data collection, analyzing and report writing by working in various reputable research organizations. She worked under direct supervision of prominent researchers of Bangladesh such as Dr. Debapriya Bhattacharya and Dr. Minhaj Mahmud.

JOB EXPERIENCES

Bangladesh Institution of Development Studies (BIDS)

Research Officer
June 2018 to Current

Center for Policy Dialogue (CPD)

Program Associate March 2018 to June 2018

Department of Economics, JU

Research Assistant

April 2017 to February 2018

Notre Dame College

Lecturer

June 2017 to August 2017

Friedrich Ebert Stiftung

Research Fellow

February 2017 to October 2017

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS

Jahangirnagar University

MSC in Economics 2015-2016

GPA- **3.77 out of 4.00** (6th out of 82 students)

Jahangirnagar University

BSC in Economics 2010- 2014

CGPA-**3.70 out of 4.00** (5th out of 109 students)

Holy Cross College

HSC in Humanities 2008 - 2010

GPA- 5.00 out of 5.00

Holy Cross Girls' High School

SSC in Humanities 2002-2008

GPA- 4.75 out of 5.00



TECHNICAL SKILLS

She has the working knowledge on basic Microsoft product such as MS Word, MS Excel and Stata. She is now eager to learn about software which are used in economics and data management related subjects. She is learning a different programming language such as R, Python, SQL and software such as ArcGIS, LaTex.

REFERENCES

Dr. Md. Amir Hussain

Pro Vice Chancellor, Department of Economics Jahangirnagar University Dhaka 1342

Phone: 01819485778

Email: amirhussainju@juniv.edu

Mohammad Amzad Hossain

Chairman.

Department of Economics Jahangirnagar University

Dhaka 1342

Phone: 01711-103844 Email: amzad104@juniv.edu

Minhaj Mahmud

Senior Research Fellow BIDS

Phone: +8802 9118999

Email: minhaj@bids.org.bd

Tanzila Sultana

Date: 7th November 2018

RESEARCH EXPOSURES

Currently working for Tracer Studies under HEQEP (1st round) under the supervision of Dr. Minhaj Mahmud.

Contributed in "HEQEP Final Round of Satisfaction Survey-2018 (HEQEP-FRSS)" under the supervision of **Dr. Minhaj Mahmud**.

Contributed in "CPD's Analysis of the Proposed National Budget FY2018-19"

Contributed in "Recommendations for the National Budget for FY2019 (Second Reading)" published by Centre for Policy Dialouge (CPD) with **Dr. Debapriya** Bhattacharya and Professor Mustafizur Rahman, Distinguished Fellows, CPD (Team Leader)

"Self-Assessment Report" on Department of Economics, Jahangirnagar University, performed under HEQEP with Professor Md. Nurul Hoque, Head of SAC, Department of Economics, Jahangirnagar University

A Research on "Economic Analysis of Geothermal Energy: A New Source of Renewable Energy" under the supervision of Dr. Shafique uz Zaman, Chairman, Department of Economics, Dhaka University

SELECTED ACHIVIEVEMENTS

- Achieved a **fellowship** from Friedrich Ebert Stiftung for University students
- GRE score 309 out of 340
- Achieved the **government scholarship** for the honors' result.
- Participated in a training program on the fundamentals of R
- Got Scholarship from Jahangirnagar University Five consecutive years For Good academic performance
- Participated in Inter and Intra college science fair and got 1st prize in both competition
- Excellent achievement in Economics in school